Mark Winston fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Teaching records, [197-?] - 2012; F-174-3; 1.95 m of textual records 773 photographs: col. slides 61 photographs 9 moving images 2 textile artifacts
  - Audio-visual and photographic materials, [197-?] - 2000; F-174-3-5; 9 moving images 419 photographs: col. slides; Physical description: includes 9 original U-matic videocassettes and 9 digital access copies.
    - Bees and Beekeeping - Anatomy and Development, 1982; F-174-3-5-0-5-2; F-174-item4, F-174-item5, F-174-item6 (2007-2012); F-174-3-5-0-0-2 (20012-2022); 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2381)
      .mov file also available in .mp4 and .mkv formats.
    - Bees and Beekeeping - Behaviour, 1982; F-174-3-5-0-5-3; F-174-item7, F-174-item8, F-174-item9, F-174-item10 (2007-2012); F-174-3-5-0-0-3 (20012-2022); 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2384)
      .mov file also available in .mkv and .mp4 format.
    - Bees and Beekeeping - Equipment and Site Selection, 1982; F-174-3-5-0-5-4; F-174-item11, F-174-item12, F-174-item13 (2007-2012); F-174-3-5-0-0-4 (2012-2022); 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2388)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item11, F-174-item12, F-174-item13.
    - Bees and Beekeeping - Spring and Summer Management, 1982; F-174-3-5-0-5-5; F-174-item14, F-174-item15, F-174-item16, F-174-item17 (2007-2012); F-174-3-5-0-0-5 (2012-2022); 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2391)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item14, F-174-item15, F-174-item16, F-174-item17.
    - Bees and Beekeeping - Swarm Prevention and the Honey Flow, 1982; F-174-3-5-0-5-6; F-174-item18, F-174-item19, F-174-item20 (2007-2012); F-174-3-5-0-0-6 (2012-2022); 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2395)
      .mov file also available in .mkv and .mp4 formats.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item18, F-174-item19, F-174-item20.
    - Bees and Beekeeping - Processing and Marketing the Crop, 1982; F-174-3-5-0-5-7; F-174-item21, F-174-item22, F-174-item23 (2007-2012); F-174-3-5-0-0-7 (2012-2022); 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2398)
      .mov file also available in mkv and .mp4 formats.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item21, F-174-item22, F-174-item23.
    - Bees and Beekeeping - Diseases and Pests, 1982; F-174-3-5-0-5-8; F-174-item24, F-174-item25, F-174-item26 (2007-2012); F-174-3-5-0-0-8 (2012-2022); 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2401)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-item24, F-174-item25, F-174-item26.
    - Bees and Beekeeping - Test and Summary, 1982; F-174-3-5-0-5-9; F-174-item27, F-174-item28 (2007-2012); F-174-3-5-0-0-9 (2012-2022); 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2403)
  - Undergraduate Semester in Dialogue and related courses, 2001 - 2012; F-174-3-6; 43 cm textual records 2 photographs
    Files in this sub-series may contain personal or confidential information. Those marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release. As a result of the review, access restrictions may apply.
    - Urban Experience 2003-3, vol. 1, 2001 - 2003; F-174-3-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-81)
    - Urban Experience 2003-3, vol. 2, 2001 - 2003; F-174-3-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-81)
    - Nature/Environment: ideas, 2001 - 2002; F-174-3-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-81)
    - Book reviews 2002-3 - Nature, Environment and Society, F-174-3-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-81)
    - 2002-3 final assignments, F-174-3-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-81)
    - Nature Environment and Society 2002-3, F-174-3-6-0-6; Includes 1 photograph (Archival box - standard 174-81)
    - Library - USD orientation, book purchases, 2002 - 2004; F-174-3-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-81)
    - Coast-to-Coast 2006 - USD course development, 2005; F-174-3-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-82)
    - Health 2012, F-174-3-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-82)
    - Religion, 2010 - 2012; F-174-3-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-82)
    - Energy, 2010; F-174-3-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-82)
    - Art in Community, 2008 - 2009; F-174-3-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-82)
    - Designing the Future spring 2009, 2007 - 2008; F-174-3-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 174-82)
    - Health: Issues and Ethics (fall 2008), vol. 1, 2007 - 2008; F-174-3-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 174-82)
    - Health: Issues and Ethics (fall 2008), vol. 2, 2007 - 2008; F-174-3-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 174-82)
    - Adaptations to Human Environmental Impact, vol. 1, 2006 - 2007; F-174-3-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 174-82)
    - Adaptations to Human Environmental Impact, vol. 2, 2006 - 2007; F-174-3-6-0-17 (Archival box - standard 174-82)
    - Adaptations to Human Environmental Impact, vol. 3, 2006 - 2007; F-174-3-6-0-18 (Archival box - standard 174-83)
    - First Nations, vol. 1, 2005 - 2006; F-174-3-6-0-19 (Archival box - standard 174-83)
    - First Nations, vol. 2, 2005 - 2006; F-174-3-6-0-20 (Archival box - standard 174-83)
    - Roseland proposal - Sustainable Community Development, 2003 - 2006; F-174-3-6-0-21 (Archival box - standard 174-83)
    - Health: Issues and Ethics (ideas), vol. 1, 2004 - 2005; F-174-3-6-0-22 (Archival box - standard 174-83)
    - Health: Issues and Ethics (ideas), vol. 2, 2004 - 2005; F-174-3-6-0-23 (Archival box - standard 174-83)
    - Health: Issues and Ethics (ideas), vol. 3, 2004 - 2005; F-174-3-6-0-24 (Archival box - standard 174-83)
    - Urban Experience 2005-1, vol. 1, 2004 - 2005; F-174-3-6-0-25 (Archival box - standard 174-84)
    - Urban Experience 2005-1, vol. 2, 2004 - 2005; F-174-3-6-0-26 (Archival box - standard 174-84)
    - 2005-1 op-eds, F-174-3-6-0-27 (Archival box - standard 174-84)
    - Art and Community, 2003 - 2004; F-174-3-6-0-28; Includes 1 photograph (Archival box - standard 174-84)
    - UniverCity Public Art Initiative, 2004; F-174-3-6-0-29 (Archival box - standard 174-84)
    - Op-ed 2004-3, F-174-3-6-0-30 (Archival box - standard 174-84)
    - Haida Gwaii - Dialogue Workshops, Field Course in Forest Management, 2008 - 2009; F-174-3-6-0-31 (Archival box - standard 174-84)
    - Banff Centre Leadership, 2008; F-174-3-6-0-32 (Archival box - standard 174-84)
- Research records, 1970 - 2014; F-174-4; 3.72 m of textual records 19 MB of textual records (electronic) 87 photographs 3,095 photographs: col. slides 40 sound recordings 14 moving images 2 multiple media documents; General note locations of special media: * Textual records in electronic form are located in sub-series 5, file 16. * Photographs are located in sub-sub-series 4-2 (files 6 and 8) and sub-sub-series 5 (file 24); the latter includes 16 digital photographs (jpeg format). * Moving images are located in sub-series 6 and include 1 film reel and 13 videocassettes (VHS). * Sound recordings are located in sub-sub-series 4-1 (3 recordings) and 4-6 (37 recordings) and include 39 audio cassettes (38 in microcassette format) and 2 digital files (aiff format). * Multiple media documents are located in sub-series 1, file 43 and are stored on optical discs (CDs).
  Series consists of records relating to Mark Winston's scholarly research and publications and includes research notes and working papers on apiculture and biology; work with artist Aganetha Dyck; newspaper and journal articles appearing in "Bee Culture," "The Vancouver Sun," "The Globe and Mail," "New York Times," and appearance on National Public Radio in the United States; research notes, drafts and published versions of scientific manuscripts; books authored by Winston; speeches, slides, and overheads used at local, national and international conferences and presentations; television interviews and media stories about Winston's research; and photographic slides pertaining to field research primarily on beekeeping, but also entomology and marine biology.
  Records include correspondence, working papers, reports, contracts, interviews, draft manuscripts, publications, slides, and audio-visual materials.
  1. General research
  2. Newspaper and journal articles
  3. Manuscripts
  4. Books
  5. Conferences and presentations
  6. Audio-visual and photographic materials
  Textual records; Photographic materials; Sound recordings; Moving images; Multi-media; Records in electronic form (born-digital)
  Most files and items in this series are open with no restrictions. However, some may contain personal or confidential information. Files or items marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release. As a result of the review, access restrictions may apply.
  Access to all analog sound recordings and moving images is restricted for preservation reasons due to the fragility of the storage medium (film reel, videocassette, audio cassette). The Archives will provide access only through digitization of the originals. As of October 2012, only one of the moving image documents (item F-174-4-6-0-0-14) exists in digital form. Please consult the reference archivist for more information about accessing these records.
  - General research, 1970 - 2008; F-174-4-1; 44.3 cm of textual records 2 multiple media documents 3 sound recordings; General note: file numbers 42, 44 and 45 have been retired and their contents registered as items.
    - Quirks and Quarks - CBC radio program, 1999; F-174-4-1-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3822)
      Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-4-1-0-40.
    - The Conscientious Kitchen (CBC Radio One program); episode 1, Flour Power, 18 October 2002; F-174-4-1-0-0-2 (Optical disc: cd OBJ-1070)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-4-1-0-45 (file).
    - The Conscientious Kitchen (CBC Radio One program); episode 23, The Colour of Honey, 30 May 2003; F-174-4-1-0-0-3 (Optical disc: cd OBJ-1070)
    - Pagurus annulipes and longicarpus, [197-?]; F-174-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Gypsy Moth experts, 1973 - 1975; F-174-4-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Dominance hierarchies in P. Longicarpus, 1975; F-174-4-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Organization for Tropical Studies, 1978 - 1979; F-174-4-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - OIRSA Project Mexico trip, 1979; F-174-4-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - UBC forests, 1981; F-174-4-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Importation permits, 1981 - 1992; F-174-4-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Prestwich, 1987 - 1991; F-174-4-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Pheromones - Chip, 1987 - 1992; F-174-4-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Pheromones - Gary, 1988; F-174-4-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Neurophysiology, 1988 - 1989; F-174-4-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Laying workers, 1988 - 1992; F-174-4-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Pheromones - races and other species, 1988 - 1993; F-174-4-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Erika Plettner, 1989 - 1994; F-174-4-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Pollination - fruit crop, 1989 - 1998; F-174-4-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 174-20)
    - Encyclopedia, 1990 - 1991; F-174-4-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Pollination - berries, 1990 - 1998; F-174-4-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Pollination - onions, 1991 - 1993; F-174-4-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Pollination - oilseed, 1991 - 1994; F-174-4-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Stickers, 1992; F-174-4-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Pollination - Rick Fisher, 1992; F-174-4-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Kiwi pollination, 1992 - 1996; F-174-4-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Hefetz, 1994 - 1995; F-174-4-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Queen rearing, 1994 - 1998; F-174-4-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Queen pheromones, 1994 - 1998; F-174-4-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Book reviews, 1994 - 1998; F-174-4-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Pheromones notes and data, vol. 1, 1994 - 1998; F-174-4-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Pheromones notes and data, vol. 2, 1994 - 1998; F-174-4-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 174-21)
    - Duncan Shaw, 1995 - 1996; F-174-4-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - Swarm-stop, 1995 - 1996; F-174-4-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - Vancouver book, 1995 - 1998; F-174-4-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - Neem, 1995 - 1998; F-174-4-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - Queen introduction experts, 1996 - 1998; F-174-4-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - [Masato] Ono, 1996 - 1999; F-174-4-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - EcoSmart Technologies, 1997 - 1999; F-174-4-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - New Zealand - Mercer, 1997 - 1999; F-174-4-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - Pankin: BP [brood pheromone], 1997 - 2000; F-174-4-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - Block: Bumble bee extract experts, 1998; F-174-4-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - Phero Tech - miscellaneous, 1998 - 2004; F-174-4-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - Robinson/Elekonich, 1999 - 2003; F-174-4-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - Aganetha Dyck installation, 2000 - 2003; F-174-4-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
      - Aganetha Dyck: Nature as Language, 2000; F-174-4-1-0-43-1 (Optical disc: cd OBJ-1068)
        Multi-media
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-4-1-0-42.
      - Aganetha Dyck: bee work at SFU, 2002; F-174-4-1-0-43-2 (Optical disc: cd OBJ-1069)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-174-4-1-0-44.
    - Gene: microarrays, 2002 - 2003; F-174-4-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 174-22)
    - "The Nature of Things" program, 2003 - 2006; F-174-4-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 174-73)
    - SFU Heavenly Honey jar labels, [199-]; F-174-4-1-0-48 (Archival box - small 174-75)
    - Swarm Team office notepad, [199-]; F-174-4-1-0-49 (Archival box - small 174-75)
    - Address book for research contacts, [199-?]; F-174-4-1-0-50 (Archival box - small 174-75)
    - Apis - African proposals, 1976 - 1979; F-174-4-1-0-51 (Archival box - small 174-75)
    - CBC Sunday Edition 2 Dec 2007 - correspondence, 2007 - 2008; F-174-4-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 174-84)
  - Newspaper and journal articles, 1994 - 2005; F-174-4-2; 25 cm of textual records
    Bee Culture Magazine; Vancouver Sun; Globe and Mail; New York Times; National Public Radio; Canadian Broadcasting Corporation
    - Bee Culture articles, 1994 - 1998; F-174-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - Bee Culture correspondence, 1994 - 2005; F-174-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1995 - 2000; F-174-4-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - Reviews, 1998 - 1999; F-174-4-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - Vancouver Sun, 1999; F-174-4-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - Globe and Mail, 1999; F-174-4-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - New York Times, 1999; F-174-4-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - Newspaper articles, 1999 - 2000; F-174-4-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - Bee Culture articles, 1999 - 2000; F-174-4-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - National Public Radio, 1999 - 2000; F-174-4-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - Vancouver Sun book reviews, [200-]; F-174-4-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - Vancouver Sun, vol. 1, 2000; F-174-4-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-23)
    - Vancouver Sun, vol. 2, 2000; F-174-4-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 174-24)
    - Reviews, 2000 - 2003; F-174-4-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 174-24)
    - Vancouver Sun, vol. 1, 2001; F-174-4-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 174-24)
    - Vancouver Sun, vol. 2, 2001; F-174-4-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 174-24)
    - Newspaper articles, 2001 - 2003; F-174-4-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 174-24)
    - Writing miscellaneous, 2001 - 2003; F-174-4-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 174-24)
    - Bee Culture articles, 2001 - 2003; F-174-4-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 174-24)
    - Vancouver Sun, 2002; F-174-4-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 174-24)
    - Reviews, 2003 - 2004; F-174-4-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 174-24)
    - Bee Culture articles, 2004 - 2005; F-174-4-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 174-24)
  - Manuscripts, 1970 - 2005; F-174-4-3; 70 cm of textual records
    - Drone comb (Lee/Winston), [197-?]; F-174-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-25)
    - Published manuscripts, 1972 - 1979; F-174-4-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-68)
    - P. Longicarpus individual recognition, 1974 - 1975; F-174-4-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-25)
    - Hermit Crab thesis, 1975 - 1976; F-174-4-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-25)
    - Hermit Crab "Animal Behaviour", 1976 - 1977; F-174-4-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-25)
    - Bombus-Apis manuscript, 1977; F-174-4-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 174-25)
    - Killer Bees study, 1977; F-174-4-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-25)
    - Mouthparts: Anthoph, 1977; F-174-4-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-25)
    - Mouthparts: Apidae, 1977; F-174-4-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-25)
    - Mouthparts: Megachil, 1977; F-174-4-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-25)
    - Age of bees in swarms, 1978; F-174-4-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-25)
    - EQC, 1978; F-174-4-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-25)
    - Intra colony demography and reproduction rate, 1978; F-174-4-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - Absconding behaviour (Winston/Taylor/Otis), 1978 - 1979; F-174-4-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - American Bee Journal papers, 1978 - 1979; F-174-4-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - Mouthpart manuscript, vol. 1, 1978 - 1979; F-174-4-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - Mouthpart manuscript, vol. 2, 1978 - 1979; F-174-4-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - Reproductive rate of bees, 1979; F-174-4-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - Seasonal patterns in African Honeybees, 1979; F-174-4-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - Factors preceding swarming (Winston/Taylor), 1979 - 1980; F-174-4-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - Demography and swarming, 1980; F-174-4-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - Swarming colony growth and management, 1980; F-174-4-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - Worker population in swarms, 1980; F-174-4-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - Cross fostering (Winston/Katz), 1980 - 1981; F-174-4-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 174-26)
    - Published manuscripts, 1980 - 1985; F-174-4-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 174-68)
    - 9-Hydroxy, 1981; F-174-4-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Age at foraging - European and Africanized bees, 1981; F-174-4-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Engorgement and weight, 1981; F-174-4-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Berry pollinators, 1981 - 1982; F-174-4-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Demography: Bee World, 1981 - 1982; F-174-4-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Fish meal - Chalmers, 1981 - 1982; F-174-4-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Factors determining temporal division of labour, 1982; F-174-4-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Diversity and Abundance of Nature Bee Pollinators (Mackenzie/Winston), 1983; F-174-4-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Trends in Canadian beekeeping, 1983; F-174-4-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Biology and Pheromone-based management of the Bumble Bee Wax Moth (Scott/Winston), 1983 - 1984; F-174-4-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Foraging Age (Winston/Fergusson), 1984; F-174-4-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Pollination in Okanogan Valley (Scott/Winston), 1984; F-174-4-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Worker weight (Lee/Winston), 1984; F-174-4-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - ABJ: Package summary, 1985; F-174-4-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Mitchell et al.: Queens, 1985; F-174-4-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Packages in BC, 1985; F-174-4-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 174-27)
    - Colony dynamics, 1985 - 1990; F-174-4-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Published manuscripts, 1986 - 1990; F-174-4-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 174-68)
    - H and H chapter [The Honey Bee Colony: Life History], 1987 - 1990; F-174-4-3-0-44 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Brood/foraging stimulation, 1987 - 1994; F-174-4-3-0-45 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Semiochemical basis of the retinue response to queen honey bees, 1988; F-174-4-3-0-46 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Apidologie (Punnett/Winston), 1988 - 1989; F-174-4-3-0-47 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Roitberg book, 1988 - 1992; F-174-4-3-0-48 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Rubink, 1988 - 1992; F-174-4-3-0-49 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - DPU, 1989; F-174-4-3-0-50 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Brood pheromone: Currie, 1989 - 1993; F-174-4-3-0-51 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - A Bee Friendly Habitat, [199-]; F-174-4-3-0-52 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Annual review of Entomology, 1990 - 1991; F-174-4-3-0-53 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Villa, J., 1990 - 1992; F-174-4-3-0-54 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - American Scientist working papers, 1991 - 1992; F-174-4-3-0-55 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - The Sciences articles, 1991 - 1992; F-174-4-3-0-56 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Published manuscripts, 1991 - 1995; F-174-4-3-0-57 (Archival box - standard 174-68)
    - American Scientist, 1992; F-174-4-3-0-58 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - The Sciences articles, 1992; F-174-4-3-0-59 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Bee World 92, 1993; F-174-4-3-0-60 (Archival box - standard 174-28)
    - Exploring Animal Behaviour: Readings from American Scientist, 1993; F-174-4-3-0-61 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Where's the Buzz, 1993; F-174-4-3-0-62 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Good fruit grower, 1993 - 1994; F-174-4-3-0-63 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - ORION Nature Quarterly, 1993 - 1994; F-174-4-3-0-64 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Anderson, Denis proposal review, 1994; F-174-4-3-0-65 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Quarterly Journal of Medicine, 1994; F-174-4-3-0-66 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Manuscript reviews, 1994 - 1995; F-174-4-3-0-67 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Equinox article, 1996; F-174-4-3-0-68 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Apidologie, 1996 - 1997; F-174-4-3-0-69 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Bio Essays reviews, 1996 - 1997; F-174-4-3-0-70 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Manuscript reviews, 1996 - 1998; F-174-4-3-0-71 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Published manuscripts, 1996 - 2000; F-174-4-3-0-72 (Archival box - standard 174-68)
    - Monique - comb, 1999; F-174-4-3-0-73 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Canadian Geographic, 2000; F-174-4-3-0-74 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
    - Published manuscripts, 2001 - 2005; F-174-4-3-0-75 (Archival box - standard 174-68)
    - Slessor, Winston and Le Conte manuscript, 2002 - 2004; F-174-4-3-0-76 (Archival box - standard 174-29)
  - Books, 1980 - 2014; F-174-4-4; 2.01 m of textual records 209 photographs: col. slides 40 sound recordings